Warren Mitofsky Papers 2008.0071
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series VI: Surveys and Studies, 1944-2006
  - Dick Morris PPA Study, 2002 (Box 16)
  - Distribution of Original Weights in NHSDA Data, 1995 (Box 16)
  - Ecological Correlations and the Behavior of Individuals, 1950 (Box 16)
  - Estimating the Incubation Period for Aids by Comparing Population Infection and Diagnosis Patterns, 1990 (Box 16)
  - For the Sake of Just and Lasting Peace, 2003 (Box 16)
  - Fintec, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Fintec – Murray Edelman, 1987 (Box 16)
  - George Fuller, 1992 (Box 16)
  - Gender and Age: Age Comparison of the Survey Sample and Actual Voters, 1972 (Box 16)
  - Global Crises, Global Solution, 2004 (Box 16)
  - Joel Buxbaum, 1990, 1994-1995, 1997 (Box 16)
  - The Kennedy-Nixon Debates: A Survey of the Surveys, 1962 (Box 16)
  - Krandel, 1971, 1984-1986, 1990-1991 (Box 16)
  - Locating Consensus for democracy: A Ten Year U.S. Experiment, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Metrorail Passenger Survey, 2001 (Box 16)
  - Nixon Administration, 1973 (Box 16)
  - Nixon vs. Media Poll, 1973 (Box 16)
  - Paul Lazarfeld, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Pew Research Center for the People and Press: Philadelphia Voter Participation Experiment, 1999 (Box 16)
  - President v. The Media, 1973-1974 (Box 16)
  - Pittsburgh Community Action Survey, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Questionnaire I, undated (Box 16)
  - Questionnaire II – Version C – AVON Customer, undated (Box 16)
  - Questionnaire II. Version N – AVON Non-customer, undated (Box 16)
  - SALT Passage Research: The State of the Art, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Selective Service Study, 1966 (Box 16)
  - Seton Hall University– Sports Poll, 2006 (Box 16)
  - Sons Fathers, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Sourcebook of Harris National Surveys, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Statistic Samples for Surveys, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Stock Market Project, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Studies in Citizen Participation in International Relations, 1959 (Box 16)
  - Survey: NYC Financial Problems, 1975 (Box 16)
  - Survey/Truth Vote Percentages, 1986-1992 (Box 16)
  - The People of South Vietnam: How They Feel About the War, A CBS Public Opinion Survey, 1967 (Box 16)
  - The Public Perspective: Who, and What, Will the “Austin 600” actually represent, 1996 (Box 16)
  - Twenty Years of Minnesota Public Opinion, 1944-1964 (Box 16)
  - University of Michigan Election Study, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Vietnam ese Studies Nationwide Opinion Survey, undated (Box 16)
  - Wirthlin Group – YATS, 1984, 1986, 1988-1990 (Box 16)
- Series VII: Political Articles and Papers, 1936-2006
  - Subseries A: Politics, 1936-2005
    - American Public Opinion and U.S. Foreign Policy, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Are There Bellwether Electoral Districts?, 1975 (Box 17)
    - Bush/Gore Articles, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Cognitive Engagement and Citizen World Views, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Communication Patterns in Presidential Primaries 1912-2000: Knowing the Rules of the Game, 1998 (Box 17)
    - Congressional Quarterly Books, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Continuity and Change in American Politics: Parties and Issues in the 1968 Election, 1969 (Box 17)
    - “Deconstructing Distrust – How Americans View Government”, 1998 (Box 17)
    - Defoliating the Grassroots: Election Day Restrictions on Political Research, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Electing the President: A Program for Reform, 1986 (Box 17)
    - Election Administration: Procedures, Problems, and Special Information, 1978 (Box 17)
    - Financing the 1972 Election by Herbert E. Alexander, 1979 (Box 17)
    - Initial Working Paper on Political Strategies, 1976 (Box 17)
    - 1976–1978 (Box 17)
    - José M. Bernardo, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Knowing It by Heart: Americans Consider the Constitution and Its Meaning, 2002 (Box 17)
    - The Making of the President, 1960 (Box 17)
    - Articles on Foreign Politics, undated (Box 17)
    - Articles on Politics, undated (Box 17)
    - Moves to Control Literacy Tests and Abolish the Poll Tax in Federal Elections, 1962 (Box 17)
    - Nomination and the Election of the President and Vice-President, 1984 (Box 17)
    - None Dare Call It Stolen: Ohio, The Election, and America’s Servile Press, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Papers regarding Clinton Scandals, 1999 (Box 17)
    - The Politics of National Convention Finances, 1968 (Box 17)
    - Presidential Campaign Issues, 1936-1991 (Box 17)
    - 1976 Presidential Debate Effects: A Hit or Miss, 1977 (Box 17)
    - Presidential Elections and the Party System, undated (Box 17)
    - Prints of Ballot Boxes, 1984 (Box 17)
    - Retro Politics: The Political Typology Version 3.0, 1999 (Box 17)
    - The Third Way Middle Class Project, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Was the 2004 Election Stolen?, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Who Knows? Political Knowledge in Comparative Perspective, 1995 (Box 17)
  - Subseries B: Politics and television, undated, 1969-1996
    - A Night at the Races: The History of Elections on Television, 1979 (Box 17)
    - Broadcasting and the Democratic Process, 1981 (Box 17)
    - Broadcasting of Political News, 1969 (Box 17)
    - CBS and the American Political Experience: A History of the CBS News Special Event and Election Units, 1983 (Box 17)
    - The Historical Evolution of Journalistic Election Reporting, undated (Box 17)
    - The Horse Race: Presidential Politics as Television Plays It, undated (Box 17)
    - How Voters Construct Images of Political Candidates: The Role of Political Advertising and T.V. News, 1994 (Box 17)
    - The Media and The People, 1995, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Articles on T.V. and Politics, undated (Box 17)
    - Presidential Primaries: The Press and Polls, undated (Box 17)
    - Public Journalism: Theory and Practice, 1994 (Box 17)
    - Tomorrow’s Communication Research, 1964 (Box 17)
    - TV Convention Coverage Patterns, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Subseries C: Voters and Voting, 1948-2006
    - A Voter Validation Experiment, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Census Files – Dissertation Materials/Mail Survey, 1968, 1975, 1980, 1986-1989, 1990, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Census Files – Dissertation Materials/Mail Survey, 1968, 1972, 1980, 1984, 1998 (Box 17)
    - Census Files – Dissertation Materials/Mail Survey, 1968, 1972, 1974, 1976, 1978, 1982, 1984-1986, 1992, 1994, 1996, 1998 (Box 17)
    - The Core of Non-Voters in Two party Elections: A Comparison Between U.S. and U.K., 2004 (Box 17)
    - Current Population Reports, The Hispanic Population in the U.S., 1993 (Box 17)
    - CRS Report for Congress: Voter Registration and Turnout, 1948-1990, 1992 (Box 17)
    - The Effect of Voter registration Laws on Voter Turnout, 1977 (Box 17)
    - Innovations in Election Administration: All-Mail-Ballot Elections, 1995 (Box 18)
    - Innovations in Election Administration: Early Voting, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Articles and Papers on Voters and Voting, undated (Box 18)
    - Pollsters Beware: New Evidence of Late Campaign Shifts in 1980 Electorate (Box 17)
    - Population Profile of the United States, 1991 (Box 17)
    - Population Profile of the United States, 1993 (Box 18)
    - Presidential Candidate Preferences According to Likelihood to Vote, 1997 (Box 18)
    - The Relationship Between Seats and Votes in Two-party Systems, 1973 (Box 18)
    - Research on American Voter Turnout: The State of the Evidence, 1981 (Box 18)
    - The True Electorate: An Examination of Voting History on Voter Registration Files, 2006 (Box 18)
    - Turnout Study, 1981 (Box 18)
    - Voters/Voter Turnout Study, 1980, 1985, 1988, 1992 (Box 18)
    - Voting Papers, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Voter Registration Papers, 1985-1989, 1992 (Box 18)
    - Voter Research Surveys, 1993 (Box 18)
    - Voter Research Surveys, 1994, 1996 (Box 18)
    - Voting for Democracy (2 Folders), 1983 (Box 18)
    - Voting Process Articles, 1994-1997 (Box 18)
    - When People Vote and What Difference It Makes, 1994 (Box 18)
- Series VIII: Professional and Organizational Materials, 1936-2006
  - AAPOR, 1979 (Box 18)
  - AAPOR, 1989 (Box 18)
  - AAPOR (2 Folders), 1992 (Box 18)
  - AAPOR, 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - AAPOR, 1993 (Box 18)
  - AAPOR 50th Anniversary, 1994 (Box 18)
  - AAPOR History, 1986, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 18)
  - AAPOR Incoming, 1993 (Box 18)
  - AAPOR Newsletter, 1980 (Box 18)
  - AAPOR Newsletter, 1997 (Box 18)
  - Absentee Registration Lists, 2003 (Box 18)
  - Advisory Council Meeting, 2004 (Box 18)
  - ASA, 1989, 1998 (Box 18)
  - Background Notes/Calls/CD Vote, undated (Box 18)
  - Board of managers Memos, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Board of Managers and Survey Committee Questions, 1992 (Box 18)
  - CBS/ CNN, 1997 (Box 18)
  - CBS Evaluation of Election Coverage, 1965-1968 (Box 18)
  - CBS Future Policy, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - CBS News Almanac, 1977 (Box 18)
  - CBS News Almanac, 1978 (Box 19)
  - CBS News Campaign Vote Analysis Handbook, 1980 (Box 19)
  - CBS News Coverage of Election Night 2000, Investigation, Analysis, and recommendations, 2001 (Box 19)
  - CBS News Directory, 2000 (Box 19)
  - CBS News Election and Survey Unit General Election Handbook (2 Folders), undated (Box 19)
  - CBS News Research – Technical Memorandum No. 1, 1967 (Box 19)
  - CBS News Research – Technical Memorandum No. 2, 1967 (Box 19)
  - CBS News Training Manual, 1969 (Box 19)
  - CBS Telephone Instruction Survey, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Certificate of Incorporation and By-laws, 1963 (Box 19)
  - CNN, 2001 (Box 19)
  - CNN, 2003-2004 (Box 19)
  - Computer Brochures, undated (Box 19)
  - Computer Help and Instructions, 1977, 1985, 1995, 1997 (Box 19)
  - Condor Petroleum, Inc., 1997 (Box 19)
  - “Conference”, 2004 (Box 19)
  - Consulta Vote Analysis Handbook, 1997 (Box 19)
  - Contact Information, 2003 (Box 19)
  - Cutler/Feinstein, 1995 (Box 19)
  - Developing Computer Reporting Systems for Elections 1972 & Beyond, 1968 (Box 19)
  - Dueling Exit Polls Story, undated (Box 19)
  - 1990 Election Campaign Effort (Box 19)
  - Edith Efron “The News Twisters”, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - ENS Market, 1994-1995 (Box 19)
  - ESC, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Evaluating a Procedure For Interviewing Voters Near the Polls, 1968 (Box 19)
  - Exit Polls, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Exit Poll Tour, 1992 (Box 19)
  - Guide to Polls and Pollsters, 1972, 1974, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Guidelines for the Public Use of Market and Opinion Research, 1981 (Box 19)
  - The Information Bank, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Intertec Consulting Group, undated (Box 19)
  - Interviewer Manual, undated (Box 19)
  - Interviewer Script, undated (Box 19)
  - Interviewer Questionnaire (2 Folders), undated (Box 19)
  - Keuffel and Esser Company Manual, undated (Box 19)
  - Krogulecki, Jones, and Stevenson Résumé, 2005 (Box 19)
  - Letters of Interest, 1990 (Box 19)
  - Lyster Watson & Company, undated (Box 19)
  - Marist Poll and Mitofsky International Agreement, undated (Box 19)
  - Memorandum on Performance of VPA, 1965 November 2 (Box 19)
  - Memoranda-- CBS, 1955, 1973, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Mitofsky International, 1997 (Box 19)
  - Mitofsky International, 2003-2006 (Box 19)
  - Mitofsky International Proposal, 1996 (Box 19)
  - Mitofsky/Market Consensus Surveys Joint Venture, 1994 (Box 19)
  - NASED Summer Conference, 2004 (Box 19)
  - NASS Summer Conference (100th Anniversary), 2004 (Box 19)
  - The National Model, 1972 (Box 19)
  - NCPP (Folder 1 of 3), 1987 (Box 19)
  - NCPP (2 Folders), 1987 (Box 20)
  - NCPP, 1990 (Box 20)
  - NCPP, 1991 (Box 20)
  - NCPP, 2001 (Box 20)
  - NCPP Conference, 1981, 1983-1984, 1987, 1989, 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - NCPP Poll Evaluation, 1936-1996, 1997 (Box 20)
  - NES Background, 1966 – 1967, 1983 (Box 20)
  - New Company Proposal, 1983 (Box 20)
  - News Research Operations Field Data Collection and Handling Procedures Manual, 1967 (Box 20)
  - Newspaper Project, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
  - “Note to Interviewers”, undated (Box 20)
  - NYAAPOR, 2005-2006 (Box 20)
  - New York Post, 2001 (Box 20)
  - Obtaining New Construction Addresses from Building Permits, 1964 (Box 20)
  - PDA, 2003 (Box 20)
  - Pearson/NCS – Vertical Systems, 2003 (Box 20)
  - Personnel – General Election, 1992 (Box 20)
  - Pew Center for Civic Journalism, 1997-2000 (Box 20)
  - POQ Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 20)
  - Press Releases, 1992 (Box 20)
  - Project to Evaluate 1984 Registration Drives (Box 20)
  - Proposal for a Clearinghouse on Voter Registration Activities, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Proposal for a Development Grant for Voter Education, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Proposal for the Recovery and Control of Assets, 1998 (Box 20)
  - Quality Control Procedure Evaluation, 1963 – 1969 (Box 20)
  - Ratings, 1946 – 1977 (Box 20)
  - Research Triangle Institute Evaluation of VNS, 2001 (Box 20)
  - RIC, 1993-1994, 1997 (Box 20)
  - RIC, 1994 (Box 20)
  - RIC, 1997-2000 (Box 20)
  - RIC, 1997-2001 (Box 20)
  - RIC 900 Call-ins (2 Folders), 1990-1993 (Box 20)
  - Roper, 2004-2005 (Box 20)
  - Roper, 2005-2006 (Box 20)
  - Roper at Age 50, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Roper Center, 1986-1988 (Box 20)
  - Roper Center, 2003-2005 (Box 20)
  - Roper Center, 2005 (Box 20)
  - Statistician Prospects, 1967 (Box 21)
  - Telephone Survey System, Time Schedule & Operations, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Verizon Project, 2002 (Box 21)
  - VNS Agreement with the Washington Post, 2000 (Box 21)
  - VNS Decision Help Screen Documentation, undated (Box 21)
  - VNS General Election Decision Screens, 2000 (Box 21)
  - VNS Guide to Editorial Screens 2000 General Election (Box 21)
  - VNS System Integration & Modernization Project, 2001 (Box 21)
  - VNS Vote Analysis Handbook, 1998 (Box 21)
  - VNS Vote Analysis Handbook, 2000 (Box 21)
  - VNS – VREPS Editorial Application Manual, 2002 (Box 21)
  - Voter Analysis Handbook – Completes, 2003 (Box 21)
  - Voter Analysis Handbook – Maps, 2003 (Box 21)
  - Voter Analysis Handbook – States, undated (Box 21)
  - VRS Administration Memos, 1990 (Box 21)
  - VRS Articles, 1990-1992, 1998 (Box 21)
  - VRS Fees for Services Provided, 1993 (Box 21)
  - VRS Interviewer Manual, 1993 (Box 21)
  - VRS Primary/Caucus Election Guide to Computer Screens, 1992 (Box 21)
  - VRS-NES Merge, 1991-1993 (Box 21)
  - VRS Vote Analysis Handbook, 1990 (Box 21)
  - VRS Vote Analysis Handbook (2 Folders), 1992 (Box 21)
  - WAPOR, 1989 (Box 21)
  - WESTAT, 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - WESTAT, 1989, 1996 (Box 21)
  - WJM Contract Release, 1974-1978, 1980-1984, 1987-1991 (Box 21)
- Series IX: Personal, Bulk, 1955-2006; 1893-2006
  - AAPOR Presidential Address, undated (Box 21)
  - Articles, 2003 (Box 21)
  - ASA Life Membership Certificate, 1985 (Box 21)
  - ASA Membership Letter, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Change of Address, 2003 (Box 21)
  - Clippings from Election Night History Project, 1996 (Box 21)
  - Clyde Tucker Memos and Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 21)
  - Clyde Tucker Memos and Correspondence, 1979-1980, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Clyde Tucker Memos and Correspondence, 1980, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Columbia University, 2005-2006 (Box 21)
  - Confidential Memorandum – Will and Estate Information, 1998 (Box 21)
  - Harvard University, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Incoming, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 22)
  - Invitations and Notices for Events, undated (Box 22)
  - Joseph Waksberg, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Letters, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Letters, 1993 (Box 22)
  - Marsh Advantage America/PHS (2 Folders), 2005-2006 (Box 22)
  - Martin Plissner and Mitofsky Papers and Articles, 1989 (Box 22)
  - M.H.S Class of 1952, 22nd Reunion, 1974 (Box 22)
  - Mid-Century Articles/Papers/Correspondence, 1955-1961, 1963-1964 (Box 22)
  - “Misc.”, 1982 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence and Postcards, undated (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, undated (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1950-1963 (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1964-1969 (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1970-1979 (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1980-1989 (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1990-2005 (Box 22)
  - Notes, undated (Box 22)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 22)
  - Articles/Papers by Mitofsky, 1994, 1996, 1998, 2000-2001 (Box 22)
  - Mitofsky Graduate School Papers, undated (Box 22)
  - Mitofsky Lectures and Talks, undated, 1981, 1982, 1985, 1995 (Box 22)
  - Methods and Standards: A Challenge for Change by Mitofsky, 1989 (Box 22)
  - “Picketing and Free Speech” and Other School Papers by Mitofsky, 1938, 1957 (Box 22)
  - Mitofsky Published Paper, 1995 (Box 22)
  - Research Papers by Mitofsky, 1977, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Mitofsky Résumés and Follow-up Letters, undated (Box 22)
  - Mitofsky School Papers, undated (Box 22)
  - National Press Club Speech, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Cartoons, undated (Box 22)
  - Old Articles, 1893,1917, 1945, 1965, 1969 (Box 22)
  - “On Warren’s Desk”, 2006 (Box 22)
  - People Power Medal of Honor, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Personal, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Personal Things, undated, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Photographs, 1984 (Box 22)
  - WJM Photographs, 1993 (Box 22)
  - Sampling Lecture, 2001 (Box 22)
  - Samuel L. Popkin, 1984-1987 (Box 22)
  - Samuel L. Popkin, 1987-1989 (Box 22)
  - Samuel L. Popkin, 1991 (Box 22)
  - Travel Plans, 1987, 1993, 2004 (Box 22)
  - University of Michigan, 1995-1996 (Box 22)
  - “Warren’s WP Index 7/7/86,”, undated (Box 22)
  - WJM Seminars, 1987 (Box 22)
  - W. Tate-Mitros Associates, Inc., 1991 (Box 22)
  - The Year of the Beard Article, 1982 (Box 22)
  - “1992” (Box 22)
- Series X: Magazines and Journals, 1976-2003
  Scope and Content Note
  [Contains individual issues of titles for the years specified and may contain gaps.]
  - American Demographics, 1981 June (Box 23)
  - The American Statistician, 2003 February (Box 23)
  - Change, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Consumer Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 23)
  - Journal of the American Statistical Association, 1978, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Nutrition Action Health Letter, 1998 May (Box 23)
  - Public Opinion, 1978-1989 (Box 23)
  - TV Guide, 1976 March 6-12 (Box 23)
- Series XI: Multimedia, undated, 1991-2003
  - Subseries A: VHS/DVD, undated, 1992-2003
    - • ABC Election Night Coverage, 11/3/92, 9:30PM-3:30AM (VHS) • CBS Election Night Coverage, 11/3/92, 9:30PM-3:30AM (VHS) • CBS News Hunger Story (VHS) • CBS News Special Report: Sixteen in Webster Groves, Feb. 25, 1966 (VHS) • CBS NewsNet Presentation • “Challenging Touchscreen Voting”, August 2003 (VHS) • CNN Election Night Coverage, 11/3/92, 9:30PM-3:30AM (VHS) • Elecciones S de Julio 1998, Noticieros Televisa, TV Azteca (VHS) • 1988 Election Night – ABC Start at 7pm (VHS) • Election Night NBC 1994 (VHS) • The 90’s: Election Special #101: The Primary, 3/26/92 (VHS) • Interview with Burns “Bud” Roper, December 2002 (VHS) • Kuralt Scenes (VHS) • Market Research Council 75th Anniversary (VHS) • “Media Matters”, 9/25/01 (VHS) • NBC Election Night Coverage, 6/2/92, 11:00PM-5:00AM (VHS) • NBC Election Night Coverage, 11/3/92. 9:30PM-3:30AM (VHS) • Rush to Judgment, 2/12/01 (VHS) • Taiwan Election Protest (2 DVD) • VRS Raw Video, 11/3/92 (VHS) (Box 24)
  - Subseries B: Audio cassettes, undated, 1994-1998
    - • Astin Interview Part 1 • Astin Interview Part 2 • AE-3 • Chran – 1 • Crossley, Gallup, Roper 11/27/95 • Crossley, Gallup, Roper, Part 1 & 3, 11/27/95 • Crossley, Roper, Gallup Part 2, 11/27/95 • Douglas Fraser • Dupert 1 • Gans Interview • Greeley • Int. Cap. (2 Cassettes) • Int. Cap. 6/11 • Int. Cap. 7/10/98 • Int. Cap. 9/28 – 2 • James McGregor Burns Interview on Direct Democracy, 2/11/94, Public Perspective Vol. 5, No. 3, part 1 • James McGregor Burns Interview on Direct Democracy, 2/11/94, Public Perspective Vol. 5, No. 3, part 2 • Jay Leve Interview • John Hostetter – Republican Congressman, Eighth Congressional District, Indiana, 12/1/94 • JSB talk by WJM: Early Election Projection Controversy, 5/1/95 • Lipset Interview Part 1 • Lipset Interview Part 2 • Mitofsky Speech, 2/28/96 • “Ta” • Ths – Tape 2 • Ths – 3 • 1 – WSJ • 2 – WSJ • “1” (Box 25)
  - Subseries C: Computer Files, undated, 1991-1997
    - • Backup – Russia: 10/2/94, Russia 2: 10/2/94 (floppy disk) • “Disk 1” (floppy disk) • File Backup, 3/24/96 (Data Cartridge) • Full Backup, 5-7-97, 1 of 2 (Data Cartridge) • Full Backup, 5-7-97, 2 of 2 (Data Cartridge) • Learn Lotus 1-2-3, 1991 (Floppy Disk) • National and All State Exit Polls Crosstabs, 2000 (CD) • State Forms (CD) • 3-D Tetris, Blackout, and Jeopardy (2 floppy disks) • Voter News Service, Nov 5, 1996, Disk 1: Nat’l, Regional, and Alab-Iowa, Disk 2: Kansas-Wyoming (2 floppy disks) • WP from AT&T Safari (3 floppy disks) (Box 25)
- Series XII: Newspapers and Oversize, undated, 1962-2004
  - Large Flyer for a Harvard Forum with Mitofsky as featured speaker, undated (Box 26)
  - The Boston Globe, 1976, 1980 (Box 26)
  - The Herald Tribune, 1996 (Box 26)
  - The Moscow Times, 1993, 1996 (Box 26)
  - The Moscow Tribune, 1993, 1996 (Box 26)
  - The National Observer, 1962 (Box 26)
  - The Not The New York Times, 1978 (Box 26)
  - The New York Observer, 1993, 2004 (Box 26)
  - The New York Post, 2000 (Box 26)
  - The New York Review of Books, 2004 (Box 26)
  - The New York Times, 1980-2005 (Box 26)
  - New York Times Magazine, 2000 (Box 26)
  - The News [Mexico City], 1994, 2000 (Box 26)
  - The Observatory, 2004 March 8 (Box 26)
  - The Times [Trenton Metro], 2001 November 4 (Box 26)
  - USA Today, 1996 June 17 (Box 26)
  - The Wall Street Journal, 1996, 2000 (Box 26)
  - The Watchman News, 1977 December 22 (Box 26)
  - The Washington Post, 1996, 2000 (Box 26)